ANONYMOUS MAJOR IDOL GROUP ADDITIONAL MEMBER AUDITION
（某大型偶像团体追加成员海选）
Why don't you become an idol with me?
要和我一起成为偶像吗？
TOTAL APPLICANTS: 136,114
（总招募人数 136114人）
1ST SCREENING: APPLICATION DOCUMENTS
（第一次评审 提交申请资料进行筛选）
SELECT FILE
（选择文件）
I LOVE IDOLS. THEY'RE LIKE FLOWERS…
（我好喜欢偶像 就像花朵一样）
PASSED (APPLICANTS: 1,288 PASS RATE: 1 IN 105.7)
（海选通过 合格人数1288人 通过率 1比105.7）
2ND SCREENING: INTERVIEW (AT 8 LOCATIONS NATIONWIDE)
（第二次评审 面试 全国设有八个面试场地）
IDOL GROUP MEMBER AUDITION
（偶像团体成员海选）
PENDING RESULTS (PREVIOUS AUDITION PASS RATE: 1 IN 12.7)
（结果待定 历次海选通过率 1比12.7）
MEGUROGAWA MIDDLE SCHOOL
（目黑川中学）
To be honest, I'm pretty confident!
老实说 我非常有信心
I wasn't qualified to apply last time, so I waited two years for this audition!
上次我没有资格申请 所以这次海选我等了两年
Yeah! I bet you passed for sure!
是的 我打赌 你肯定能通过
Since you're cute and good at dancing too, Ruby!
因为露比你又可爱 又擅长跳舞
-Though your singing is, you know. -"You know"?
-虽然你的歌声… 你懂的 -什么？
But you're appealing enough to cover up that flaw, Ruby!
但你的魅力足以掩盖你的缺陷 露比
"Flaw"?
“缺陷”？
Anyhow, I'm definitely gonna pass this idol audition!
不管怎样 我一定能通过这次偶像海选
And one day, I'll become a top idol like my mom.
总有一天 我会成为像妈妈一样的顶级偶像
My name is Ruby Hoshino.
我的名字叫星野露比
I have two secrets that I can't even tell my friends.
我有两个秘密 连我闺蜜都不知道
Over a decade ago, the legendary idol who was murdered by a cult fan stalker,
十几年前 那个被狂热粉丝 跟踪、谋杀的传奇偶像
Ai, was my mother.
爱 就是我的母亲
And one more.
还有一个秘密
The fact that I have memories of my previous life.
事实上 我还保留着对前世的记忆
My body was weak since birth, so I spent most of that life in a hospital.
上一世 我从出生就很虚弱 所以大部分时间都是在医院度过的
The only fun I could have was with idol otaku activities.
我唯一的乐趣就是看偶像御宅族活动
And I was especially obsessed with Ai from B Komachi.
我特别痴迷于B小町组合里的爱
Even in the last hours of my life,
即使在我生命的最后几个小时
Ai's singing voice was echoing inside my head.
爱的歌声仍在我脑海中回荡
But the next time I woke up, I was reborn as Ai's child.
但当我再次醒来时 我重生为爱的孩子
Ai…
爱…
Those couple of years until Mama died are a treasure to me.
妈妈去世前的那几年对我来说很珍贵
I will become like Mama!
我会变得像妈妈一样
It's okay to dream, but high school entrance exams are around the corner.
有梦想可以 但中考马上就要到了
You don't get it, Bro.
你不懂 哥
I'm gonna become an idol.
我要成为偶像
Schools with entertainment courses prioritize interviews.
开设演艺科的学校 会优先考虑面试成绩
Academic skills are only for reference.
学术技能仅供参考
I don't have to study if I become an idol. I can kill two birds with one stone!
如果我成为偶像 我就不用学习了 简直一石二鸟
Don't gamble your life away with some tidbit you got somewhere.
不要把你的生活赌在某些小道消息上
You can dream of becoming an idol, but being an idol is no glamorous dream.
你可以梦想成为偶像 但成为偶像并不是个迷人的梦想
Low pay is standard and you'll have to retire before you're 30.
低工资很普遍 而且30岁前就得隐退
And your daily life will always be under fan surveillance.
你的日常生活 永远会在粉丝的监视之下
The industry survival rate's low after idol graduation
这个行业的存活率很低 偶像毕业后
and the majority shifts to a different field in the end.
大多数人最终都转行了
A job with the cost and benefit being this mismatched is rare.
成本和收益如此不匹配的工作 非常罕见
So what are you saying?
你到底想说什么？
Life's about doing what you want!
人生不就是做自己想做的事吗
If you worry about cost or benefit, you can't do anything!
如果你担心成本或收益 就什么都做不了
There are people who end their lives not being able to do anything!
有些人即便在生命结束之时 也什么都做不了
I don't want that!
我不想那样
Suit yourself.
随便你
I'm going to the director's place.
我去导演家了
My brother has changed since Mama died.
妈妈死后 哥哥就变了
He always has a glum face on and never seems like he's having fun.
他总是一副愁眉苦脸的样子 从来都不开心
He's been up to something after he began studying under the director,
自从他开始在导演手下学习后 就一直在密谋着什么
but he won't tell me anything.
但他什么都不告诉我
My brother isn't the only one who changed.
改变的人不只哥哥而已
We lost contact with Mr. Ichigo after that incident,
那件事之后 一护先生跟我们失联了
so Mrs. Miyako took over the business.
所以京子夫人接手了公司
B Komachi, who lost their star Ai, disbanded two years after.
失去明星爱的B小町在两年后解散了
The current Ichigo Production has no idol division
目前 莓制作公司没有偶像部门
so it extended its business to managing internet personalities to get by.
所以 为了维持经营 把业务拓展到管理网络红人上
Hey, aren't you ever going to make another idol group?
你不打算再组建一个偶像团体吗？
It's not as easy as you say.
这可不像你说的那么容易
If I could, I would.
如果可以的话 我会的
The dream Ai showed us was an unforgettable experience.
爱带给我们的梦想是一次难忘的经历
1ST PLACE YEARLY RANKING
（年度排名 音乐类 第一名 B小町）
But we need to think of that as winning the lottery.
但我们需要把这当成是中了彩票
The longer I do this job, the more I can tell.
我做这份工作的时间越长 我知道的就越多
That kind of miracle won't happen again.
这种奇迹不会再度发生
Things usually don't go that smoothly in real life.
在现实生活中 事情通常不会那么顺利
Besides…
此外…
Besides?
此外？
Uh.
那…
Nothing. You should be getting your call for your audition results soon.
没什么 你应该很快就会接到 告知海选结果的电话
If you pass, you've agreed to join their agency, right?
如果你通过海选 你就会同意 加入他们的经纪公司 对吧？
They're a much proper agency than us.
他们比我们更合适
Well, that is true, but…
话是这么说 但是…
AUDITION
（来电：海选）
Speak of the devil.
说曹操曹操到
Yes?
您好？
Am I speaking with Ms. Ruby Hoshino?
您是星野露比女士吗？
Yes, this is Hoshino!
是的 我是星野
Yes.
是的
Oh, I see.
这样啊
Thank you.
谢谢
Then we look forward to your participation next time.
那么 我们期待您下次参与
Ruby.
露比
I didn't make it.
我没通过…
That's reality.
这就是现实
There are all kinds of business politics,
商业政治无处不在
so you can't expect your talent to be fairly evaluated.
所以 你没法指望你的才能 能得到公平的评判
Not everyone can be like Ai.
不是每个人都能像爱一样
GOTANDA STUDIO GOTANDA
（五反田工作室 五反田）
Thanks, Director.
谢谢你 导演
You can even fool your own twin sister, so you're pretty good as an actor.
你甚至能骗过自己的双胞胎妹妹 真是位优秀的演员
What if the real agency calls her?
如果真正的经纪公司 给她打电话怎么办？
I sent a text message from Ruby's phone to the agency saying she'll withdraw,
我用露比的手机 给经纪公司发了条短信 说她会退出
and I blocked their phone number as well.
我还屏蔽了他们的电话号码
I know what I'm doing.
我知道自己在做什么
I don't understand you.
我不明白
Why go that far to crush your sister's dream?
为什么要如此破坏你妹妹的梦想？
That girl's a real beauty, she may actually have a chance.
那女孩是个美女 可能真的有机会
No need to tell me.
不用你说
But I won't let Ruby become an idol.
但我不会让露比成为偶像
I won't let her make the same mistake that Ai made.
我不会让她重蹈爱的覆辙
Ever.
永远不会
You and your sister complex. You're overprotective.
你这妹控 你过度保护她了啊
Just myself is enough.
我自己就够了
I'll carry the plan out by myself.
我会自己执行计划
You were scouted?!
星探找上你了？
Yup! But it's for those so-called underground idols!
是的 但是是去做地下偶像
I think this must be destiny!
我想这一定是命运
I've been eyeing underground idol hiring ads for a while!
我关注地下偶像招聘广告 有一段时间了
You know how Mama became an idol from being scouted too?
你知道妈妈是怎么被星探发现 成为偶像的吗？
So, don't you think I'm being led down this path?
所以 你不觉得 是她引向我走上这条路吗？
Are you sure that's really an idol group?
你确定那真的是偶像团体吗？
Not some shady job?
不是什么见不得人的工作？
It's nothing like that.
不是那样的
Did you check what's in their contract?
你检查过他们的合同里有什么吗？
He said he'll show me their concert soon and that we'd go over the contract after.
他说很快就会给我看他们的演唱会 然后我们再看一遍合同
Huh.
-什么？
I'm so excited!
我太期待啦！
Jeez, what a pain.
天啊 真要命
I gotta find some way to stop her.
我得想办法阻止她
There you go again.
你又来了
Because of Ai's case,
因为爱的案子
I can understand how you don't want your beloved sister to follow in her footsteps.
我能理解你的心情 不想让心爱的妹妹步爱的后尘
Even I…
即使是我
still think about what it'd be like now had I done something different back then.
也会想 如果我当时做了不同的事情 现在会是什么样子
I never want to feel like that again.
我再也不想有那种感觉了
I raised Ruby like she was my own daughter.
我把露比当亲生女儿养大
I swore I would protect her.
我发誓我会保护她
But because she's my daughter, I can't stop Ruby from pursuing her dreams.
但也正因为露比是我女儿 我不能阻止她追求梦想
She's starting to look more and more like AI.
她长得越来越像爱了
And unfortunately, she does have potential.
不巧的是 她确实有潜力
Either way, she would've ended up this way.
不管怎样 她都会变成这样
Before we decide, there's something I need to do.
在我们决定之前 我还有件事要做
I'm borrowing the agency's card.
我要借用公司的名片
What?
什么？
What are you going to do?
你打算做什么？
Hello!
你好
Can I have a minute?
我们能单独聊聊吗？
What is it?
什么事？
I'm from here.
我来自这里
Oh, Ichigo Production?
莓制作公司？
You know us?
你知道我们？
Yes, B Komachi's agency, right? My mom was a fan!
是的 B小町的经纪公司 对吧？ 我妈妈过去是粉丝
Wow!
天啊
So this is Ichigo Production!
这就是莓制作公司啊
You're so young,
星探先生你这么年轻
so I thought you were a recruiter for a shady job.
我还以为 你要拉我做什么不好的工作
This feels like a shady nightmare.
感觉这就像一场阴暗的噩梦
First off, I'm going to investigate the group that Ruby was scouted to.
首先 我要调查一下 招募露比的那个团体
Since there's all sorts of underground idols.
因为地下偶像良莠不齐
If they're a worthless management, we won't even consider it.
如果他们的管理层一无是处 我们连考虑都不会考虑
We can talk about Ruby becoming an idol or not after that.
在那之后 我们再讨论露比能不能当偶像
Lala, you're currently working under an agency called Yilibu, right?
拉拉 你现在的经纪公司 叫伊里布 对吧？
Yes.
对
We'd like to offer you a better set of conditions.
我们想给你提供更好的条件
What kind of conditions are you working under right now?
你现在在什么样的环境下工作？
Um.
那个…
A small guaranteed minimum income under the condition of doing all concerts.
在完成所有演唱会的前提下 可以拿到最低收入
And at the photo event after the concerts,
在演唱会结束后的拍照活动中
there's a commission based on the number of photos taken.
会根据拍摄照片的数量获得佣金
That's our main income.
这是我们主要的收入来源
Then our outfit and various costs are deducted from there.
然后再扣除服装和各种费用
Since transportation and makeup fees are out of pocket too,
因为交通费和化妆费都是自理
we don't make 100,000 yen a month most of the time.
所以大多数时候 我们一个月挣不到十万日元
Hmm.
嗯
Any complaints about your current group?
你对现在的团体有什么不满吗？
Of course!
当然有了
Management's pushing for this one girl, but they over-favor her like crazy!
管理层一直在推这个女孩 但他们对她偏心得也太过分了
Why? Because apparently, that girl's dating management.
原因很明显 那个女孩在跟管理层的人约会
Oh jeez.
天啊
It's not like she's good at singing. Nor does she have a great face.
她不唱歌唱不好 长得也不好看
She steals other members' customers by luring them to crush on her.
她会通过引诱 来挖角其他成员的客户
I'm doing this seriously,
我工作很认真
but we can't become a hit because of half-hearted management!
但我们红不起来 就是因为那偏心的管理层
I feel nothing but bad vibes in the group, and I sense some members quitting.
团体里的氛围也很差 一些成员可能要退出了
And I hear management is scouting like crazy too.
我听说管理层也在疯狂地发掘新人
If I can move to Ichigo Production…
如果我能进入莓制作公司…
There are underground idol management that have experience,
有很多地下偶像经纪公司 是经验丰富的
but there are many idol lovers who do it as an extension of their hobby too.
但也有很多是偶像爱好者 在经营自己的爱好而已
Of course, we don't know if that girl's story was even true.
当然 我们甚至不知道 那个女孩的故事是不是真的
Jealousy and conflicts between members
成员之间互相嫉妒、发生冲突
and complaints toward management producing false rumors are common.
以及制造谣言 抹黑管理层 这种不满都很常见
First of all, managing a group of young girls is extremely difficult.
毕竟 管理一群年轻女孩 就已经很不容易了
Even with B Komachi,
即使在B小町
Ai was the most popular, so favoritism was…
爱也是最受欢迎的 所以偏心的程度…
Ugh, just the thought of it makes me sick.
光是想想就让我恶心
Either way, we're not letting Ruby join a group where rumors rise like that.
不管怎样 我们都不会让露比 加入一个谣言四起的团体
Then what are you going to do?
那你打算怎么办？
There's countless things. Like hire a detective and expose them online…
办法有很多 比如雇个侦探在网上曝光他们
Don't make jokes like that.
不要开这种玩笑
It isn't a joke.
我没开玩笑
I don't intend on letting Ruby become an idol.
我本就不打算让露比成为偶像
At least not under a management that isn't trustworthy.
现在至少不能让她跟着 不值得信任的管理层
By the way, how about we really hire that girl?
对了 我们不如真的招那个女孩来？
You know we don't manage idols anymore.
你知道我们不再经营偶像了
Besides, I don't want to hire someone who talks badly about her group members.
另外 我也不想雇佣 一个会说其他成员坏话的人
Please excuse me for the day.
今天我先下班了
Goodnight.
辛苦了
Ta-da! Hey, what do you think?
你们觉得怎么样？
You look cute.
很可爱的
You gotta dress up on your important days!
果然在重要的日子里 就得盛装打扮
-Ah, I'm so excited! -She really does.
-好期待 -她真的很期待啊
Ruby, you're serious, huh?
露比 你是认真的吧？
Yeah.
是的
You do know that the world you're about to enter is a tough place?
你知道你即将进入的世界很艰难吧？
You may feel miserable for not becoming a hit idol.
你可能会因为没有成为热门偶像 而感到痛苦
It's not just the salary, your private life--
不仅仅是薪水 还有你的私生活…
I know! Aqua told me the same thing.
我知道 阿夸也是这么跟我说的
Even stalking is a common story you'll hear about every day.
甚至被跟踪也是家常便饭
Despite that--
尽管如此…
Of course! I mean, I can become one.
当然知道 我的意思是 我可以成为偶像
I can finally become an idol too.
我终于可以成为偶像了
I swear I'll become just like Mama!
我发誓 我会变得像妈妈一样
You're serious?
你是认真的？
I'm serious!
我是认真的
Then do not join that group.
那就不要加入那个团体了
What? Why?
什么？为什么？
I want to seriously become an idol--
我真的想成为一个偶像…
If you're serious, then join our agency.
如果你是认真的 那就加入我们公司吧
Ichigo Production will launch a new idol group for the first time in over a decade.
莓制作公司将在十多年来 首次推出一个新的偶像团体
Stamp your seal here on the binding.
在骑缝处盖上你的章
Seal on the binding?
在骑缝处盖章？
I don't really understand, but I just stamp here?
我不太明白 在这儿盖章？
EXCLUSIVE CONTRACT
（独家合同）
HOSHINO
（星野）
Okay, now you are an artist belonging to Ichigo Production, Ruby.
好了 露比 现在你是莓制作公司的艺人了
If you do anything bad, I'll sue you.
如果你做了什么坏事 我就起诉你
That's super scary.
这太可怕了
It's not a joke, okay?
这不是玩笑 知道吗？
This is also a necessary step to enter the entertainment course,
这也是进入演艺科的必要步骤
so don't get mad, Aqua.
所以不要生气 阿夸
I'm not exactly against it.
我并不完全反对
GOTANDA STUDIO GOTANDA
（五反田工作室 五反田）
Aqua, welcome!
阿夸 欢迎啊
Is the director awake?
导演醒了吗？
He's sleeping, but you can go ahead and slap him awake.
他在睡觉 但你可以去拍醒他
Do you want to eat with us again?
你还想跟我们一起吃饭吗？
No, don't mind me.
不了 不用管我
Oh, you're here.
你来了
Good morning.
早上好
Edit this, so it looks good.
往好的方向改改
Roger.
好的
I'm still a middle school student.
我还是个中学生
I'm not old enough for a job, so I can't gain experience on set.
没到可以打工的年龄 所以我不能在片场积累经验
That's why I'm working under the director as his pupil,
所以我在导演手下工作 跟他学习
helping him with film production.
帮他制作电影
I see.
这样啊
So your sister's gonna go down the path of an idol after all.
所以你妹妹还是要走上偶像之路了
You're okay with it? As her brother?
你没意见吧？作为她的哥哥？
Rather than having her become an idol in some group from who-knows-where,
与其让她加入 不知从哪里冒出来的偶像团体
she'll be in safe hands if her management is family.
不如让她待在自己家的经纪公司 这样安全些
Brother and sister both choose the path of entertainment, huh?
兄妹二人都选择了演艺圈 是吗？
Not both. My goal is to work backstage now.
并不是 我现在的目标是在幕后工作
Weren't you gonna become an actor again?
你不打算再当演员吗？
You're applying to your sister's school, right?
你申请的学校 不是和你妹妹是同一所吗？
Only Ruby's taking the entertainment course. I'm taking the general.
只有露比读演艺科 我读一般科
When you came to study under me,
你来跟我学习的时候
you looked like you definitely wanted to become an actor.
看起来很想成为一名演员
For me, becoming an actor is just a stepping stone.
对我来说 成为演员只是一块垫脚石
To find the guy who put Ai to death.
找到杀害爱的凶手
To find my father to give him a taste of the pain Ai went through.
找到我的父亲 让他尝尝爱所经历的痛苦
Oddly enough, the key to finding him is myself.
奇怪的是 找到他的关键竟是我自己
I should be able to identify him through DNA testing his hair or saliva.
我应该可以通过他的头发或唾液 进行基因检测 来确认他的身份
But in order to do that,
但为了做到这一点
I need to get to a position where I can interact with those in showbiz.
我需要处在一个 可以与演艺圈的人互动的位置上
Becoming an actor is the fastest way for that,
成为演员是最快的方法
but if I just need to be in showbiz, I can just work as an AD or backstage.
但如果我只是需要进入演艺圈 当副导演或者幕后工作都是可以的
Although they were minor roles, I can tell after performing in a few of your works.
虽然我演的都是小角色 但演过你的几部作品后 我就看出来
I don't have a talent for acting.
我没有表演天赋
I was just one of the many struggling actors out there
我只是众多努力奋斗的演员中的一员
who try hard but can't get anywhere.
他们很努力 但却一事无成
I don't have a special skill of my own like Ai did.
我不像爱那样 有自己的特殊技能
I shouldn't aim for a goal that's beyond my abilities.
我不应该追求 超出我能力范围之外的目标
If a kid doesn't dream, who will?
如果一个孩子不做梦 谁会做梦呢？
Even as a college student, it'd still be too early to give up on your dreams.
即便上了大学 放弃梦想仍然为时过早
Listen,
听着
here's some advice from a middle-aged guy chasing his dream for 20 years.
以下是一位追逐梦想20年的 中年男子的一些建议
I'm only gonna say it once, so listen up.
我只说一次 所以听好了
Everyone has a right to dream.
每个人都有权利拥有梦想
Same with the lottery, you'll n--
跟买彩票一样 你会…
Taishi! The food's ready!
泰志 饭好了
M-Mom! I was giving a really nice talk, so don't interrupt us!
妈妈 我正要慷慨陈词 所以不要打断我们
How was I supposed to know that?!
我怎么会知道？
If I waited, the miso soup would've gotten cold!
如果我等着 味增汤就凉了
I'll come over once we finish talking!
我们一聊完我就过去
There was a time when I was struggling just like you.
曾经有一段时间 我和你一样挣扎
-Oh, my! -But…
-天啊 -但是…
Look at all this mess here! Gosh!
看看这些乱七八糟的东西 天啊
Will you just hurry and go?!
你能不能快点出去？
Honestly, this child!
这孩子！
Hey, you're already in your mid-forties, why don't you leave the nest soon?
你都四十多岁了 为什么不早点搬离老家？
There's no benefit to leaving your parent's house if it's in the city!
如果父母的房子在城市里 那离开父母的房子没有任何好处！
There's actually a ton of guys like me! It's typical in the creative field!
像我这样的男人其实有很多 特别是在创意领域
Anyway, you'll never win the lottery if you don't buy a ticket. You need…
不管怎样 如果你不买彩票 就永远没法中奖 你需要…
The words of a man living in his childhood room doesn't sink in.
这个至今仍住在童年房间里的男人 他说的话 我听不进去
There was a time when I believed I had talent like Ai.
曾几何时 我相信我有爱那样的天赋
But I couldn't become like Ai--
但我没法变得像爱一样…
Ai this, Ai that! Shut up, you sound like a pirate.
爱这个、爱那个的 烦死了 跟猴子一样哎哎叫
It's true Ai was incredible. Maybe she really was a special person.
爱确实令人难以置信 也许她真的是个特别的人
But you can never become Ai, and Ai can never become you.
但你永远无法成为爱 爱也永远无法成为你
Did Ai ever have the filmmaking skills like you have right now?
爱有像你现在这样的 电影制作技巧吗？
Did she have a brain like you?
她有像你这样的大脑吗？
Don't chicken out just from being defeated one or two times.
不要因为被打败一两次就退缩
Say that type of thing after you use all the resources you have first.
在你穷尽了所有资源之后 再说这种话
It's way too early for you to be acting like an average person.
现在就说自己资质平平 还为时过早
You wanna be an actor, right?
你想当演员 对吧？
It's written on your face.
都写在你脸上了
And maybe Aqua might be an actor?
也许阿夸会当演员？
Hey, Director.
导演
Hm?
什么？
I--
我…
Aqua, you'll eat here, right? I'll go and serve your rice already!
阿夸 你会在这里吃吧？ 我这就去给你端饭
Mature Baby was just about to say something good right now!
小大人刚想说点积极的话呢！
Don't come in!
不要进来！
How could I have known?!
我怎么会知道？
This is Youtou High School.
这里是阳东高中
It's a six-year secondary school with a rare entertainment course.
这是一所集初中和高中为一体的 六年制中学 有罕见的演艺科课程
But not everybody can take this course.
但不是每个人都能上这门课
A certificate proving you belong to a talent agency is required.
需要出示隶属于某家经纪公司的证明
I'm Ruby Hoshino from Ichigo Production!
我是莓制作公司的星野露比
GENERAL COURSE INTERVIEW HALL
（一般科课程面试会场）
I'm Aquamarine Hoshino…
我是星野爱久爱海
That's some name you have…
你的名字真厉害
A standardized score of 70?!
70分的标准分数？
Our school is recommended for those who score around 40…
为什么会来我们学校？ 这里是推荐给40分左右的学生的
I was drawn to your spirit.
我被你们的精神吸引了
You were drawn to our school spirit that much?!
你这么喜欢我们的校风？
MEDICAL SCHOOL GRADUATE
（东京国立医大毕业生）
How was it?
怎么样？
Probably okay. And you?
应该没问题 你呢？
No problems.
没问题
If by some chance I don't get in, it'd be because of my name.
如果我碰巧没被录取 那一定是因为我的名字
That's true, your real name is Aquamarine Hoshino after all.
没错 毕竟你的真名是星野爱久爱海
Though everybody just shortens it and calls you Aqua.
不过大家都嫌长 直接叫你阿夸
Aqua?
阿夸？
Hm?
什么？
Aqua Hoshino?!
星野阿夸？
Aqua! Aqua?
阿夸
You're Aqua Hoshino?!
你是星野阿夸？
Who were you again?
你是谁？
Oh, isn't she that kid?
她不是那个孩子吗？
The genius child actress who licks baking soda.
那个十分爱舔苏打的天才童星
who can cry in ten seconds!
是十秒钟就能哭出来的天才童星
We were cast in a film together! I'm Kana Arima!
我们一起演过一部电影 我是有马加奈
Ah, long time no see. You were in the entertainment course here?
好久不见 你在这里读演艺科吗？
I'm so glad. I thought you quit for the longest time.
太好了 很久以来 我以为你退圈了
I finally got to see you.
我终于见到你了
Are you taking our entertainment course?! Are you?!
你要读我们的演艺科吗？是吗？
No, I applied for the general course.
不是 我申请了一般科课程
Why?!
为什么？
Subtitle translation by: Kanami Kitabayashi
字幕翻译：宋宛娇